In the previous video, I brought up
在之前的课程中
a few questions we'll be exploring throughout this lesson.
我提出了四个即将探索的问题
First, let's take a look at the data and see how we might answer the first question
先来浏览数据 看看如何回答第一个问题
about how to break into the field of
根据调查结果 如何入门 成为一名开发者
To get started, let's read in the necessary libraries,
开始之前 先导入几个必要的库
we will need to wrangle our data, pandas and numpy.
用于数据清理的 Pandas 和 NumPy
If we decide to build some basic plots,
如果我们想要绘制基础的图表
we might also want matplotlib.
那就需要用到 Matplotlib
Now, to look at the first question of interest,
现在 来看一下第一个问题
what are those important industries suggest to help others break into the field.
从业者对新手入门的建议是什么
Looking at the CousinEducation field,
CousinEducation 这一列
you can see exactly what these individuals would suggest to help others.
包含了调查参与者对其他人的帮助建议
Below, you can take a look at the full field that the survey participants would see.
下面 你能看到所有参加调查问卷的人都能看到的完整字段
Let's take a look at what the participants had to say.
我们看看问题选项有哪些
"Oh this wasn't what I was expecting.
这并不是我想要的效果
Is grouping items together,
如果参与者选择了一条以上的建议
if a participant provided more than just one answer."
就会把所有选项都放在一起
Let's see if we can clean this up.
我们来看一下 是否能清理该数据
First, let's change this index column to have a more appropriate name.
首先 把 index 列名改成更合适的名称
I'll change it to method.
修改为 method (方法)
Now, with a quick look through the data,
在大概浏览完数据之后
we can create a list of the individual methods that were marked by a user.
我们可以创建一个包含所有方法选项的列表
I also can find this in the documentation.
其实也可以在调查问卷的文档中找到这些选项
You could additionally write something that went in and parsed by
你也可以编写一个函数 输入每一行的文字
semicolons that grab the distinct values within each of these blocks,
用分号分割为不同的选项
and then basically just put them into a set,
然后放入一个集合 (set) 中
so that you only had one of each.
这样就不会有重复项了
Here's my list of values.
这里是我的选项列表
Now, we want to see how often each of these individual values appears.
现在 我们来看一下 列表中每一个选项的频数
I wrote this function to assist with the process.
我写了一个函数来完成操作
It isn't the best solution but it gets the job done and
这并不是最好的解决方案 不过能够满足需求
our dataset isn't large enough to computationally hurt us too much.
还好我们的数据量不大 不会占用太多计算资源
Now, we can apply the function.
现在我们可以应用该函数
Notice that I tried to provide a doc string that would allow
需要注意的是 函数里提供了一些文档字符串
a user to use this without really understanding what's going on in the code here.
这样别人不用完全理解代码的逻辑 也可以正确使用该函数
It provides the inputs for the user and then the specified output.
其向用户提供了输入和指定输出的说明
This is a really important process for future
这是非常重要的流程 不论是对未来的你
you and other software engineers you might be working with.
还是对其他有合作机会的软件工程师
Here, I'm applying it,
在这里 我调用了该函数
so you can see that I'm passing it,
你可以看到
the study data frame that we had above,
我传入了前面定义过的 study DataFrame
I'm passing it the method column, the count column,
以及 method 和 count 这两个列名
and then I'm passing it the possible value which is the list that I created up here.
然后再传入 possible_vals 我之前创建的列表
These are the two column names in the study data frame and
这是 study DataFrame 里的两个列名
then this is the list that we're looking for.
然后这个是我想要查找的选项列表
Now, using our function to take a look at the results,
现在 可以看到该函数返回的结果
it looks like good news for you, Dasidy.
看上去对优达学诚是好消息
Most individuals think that you should take online courses,
大多数的人认为应该参加网络课程
but we can actually look at this as a percent.
我们也可以把频数转换成百分比
You can see that almost 21 percent of the individuals suggested to take online courses,
你可以看到 将近 21% 的人都建议参加网络课程
more than any of the other methods.
比其他任何方法都要多
We might want to take this one step further and say,
我们还可以更进一步
we care more about the methods that are suggested by those who earn more,
可能我们会更关心 收入高或者工作满意度较高的开发者给出的建议
Let's take a stab at incorporating that into this analysis.
我们将这些因素纳入分析
I updated the function that we were using before to be able to look
我更新了之前的函数 使其结果可以展现出
at how salary was related to each of these methods that we see here.
这里每个方法与工资之间的联系
I provided the code for you in the workspace on the next page.
在下一页的 Workspace 中可以找到该函数的代码
You can see, using this function in this case did hurt us.
你可以看到 这种情况下使用该函数会非常头疼
This function takes forever to run.
其运行效率极低
Computationally, we need to find a better solution.
从计算的角度 我们需要一个更好的解决方案
Once that gets done running,
这一步运行完毕后
we'll want to sort this by the mean column.
我们想要按照 mean_col 来重新排序
That is, we want the highest value,
也就是说 具备最高平均收入的推荐方法排在最前面
The ending table that you get from the results should look like this.
最终得到的结果应该是这样的
Here is the number of individuals that suggested this method.
这里是推荐这种方法的人数
You can see that this is different than the results that we saw
你可以发现这个排序跟我们之前看到的不一样
earlier and that's because not everyone had a salary.
因为不是所有的人都是有收入的
So those individuals were not included in this dataset.
他们并没有包含在数据中
Here is the mean salary for the individuals who suggested this method,
这里是推荐这种方法人的平均收入
and then over here on the end,
最后这几列
I provided a 95 percent confidence interval around this mean salary,
还可以看到 收入均值的 95% 置信区间
as was the standard deviation and variance.
以及标准偏差和方差
By looking through these values,
观察这些数值
we can sort of see if there's overlap that
我们可以看看是否存在重叠
suggests there is'nt a significant difference between the methods,
如果没有的话 那就说明方法之间没有显著差异
whereas if there is an overlap,
如果存在重叠
that does suggest that there's a significant difference.
则说明方法之间存在显著差异